{"metadata":{"generator":"Captivate","generatorVersion":"11.0.1","schemaVersion":"","author":"author","title":"","description":"project description","email":"author@company.com","website":"www.company.com","tags":"","thumbnail":"","source":"assets","durationInFrames":720,"frameRate":30,"totalSlides":8,"width":1024,"height":627,"responsive":true,"scalable":false,"launchFile":"index.html","isVRProject":false},"contentStructure":[{"id":"Text_Caption_16","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_16","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_15","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_15","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Button_7","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_7","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si32105","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si32119","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Button_8","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_8","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si32185","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si32210","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Slide5366","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Text_Caption_16","Text_Caption_15","Button_7","si32105","si32119","Button_8","si32185","si32210"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide5366"}}},{"id":"Click_Box_6","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Click_Box_6","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Button_9","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_9","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si32374","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si32400","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_17","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_17","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Image_2","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_2","roles":{}},{"id":"Slide32251","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Click_Box_6","Button_9","si32374","si32400","Text_Caption_17","Image_2"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide32251"}}},{"id":"Click_Box_4","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Click_Box_4","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Button_4","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_4","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si27062","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si27075","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_5","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_5","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_6","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_6","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide27179","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"Content3","thumbnail":"","children":["Click_Box_4","Button_4","si27062","si27075","Text_Caption_5","Text_Caption_6"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide27179"}}},{"id":"Click_Box_5","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Click_Box_5","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Button_5","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_5","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si30705","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si30731","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_9","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_9","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_10","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_10","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Image_1","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_1","roles":{}},{"id":"Slide30524","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Click_Box_5","Button_5","si30705","si30731","Text_Caption_9","Text_Caption_10","Image_1"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide30524"}}},{"id":"si27682","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_7","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si27719","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"__fbbgitem_h8v11_FB_MS5_14","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide27916q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si27707","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_8","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si27753","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"1","roles":{}},{"id":"si29811","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si29815","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si29811_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"type the answer here richtig - \r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si29826","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si29830","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si29826_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"type the answer here","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si29841","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si29845","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si29841_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"type the answer here","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si29856","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si29860","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si29856_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"type the answer here","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si27839","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_1","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide27916q0","for":"Slide27916q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si27851","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide27916q0","for":"Slide27916q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si27863","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide27916q0","for":"Slide27916q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si28218","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide27916q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si27798","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_2","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide27916q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si28499","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide27916q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si28525","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide27916q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide27916","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si27682","si27707","si29815","si29830","si29845","si29860","si27839","si27851","si27863","si27798","si28499"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide27916"},"question":{"interactionId":"27669","quizId":379,"title":"Multiple Choice\r","text":"Type the question here","ikc":true,"type":"knowledgeCheck","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":["A"]}}},{"id":"si30229","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_22","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si30266","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"__fbbgitem_h8v11_FB_MS6_70","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide30523q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si30254","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_27","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si30322","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"1_9","roles":{}},{"id":"si30278","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_43","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si30282","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_44","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si30278_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"24","roles":{"answer":{"title":"type the answer here Riuchtig\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si30289","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_45","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si30293","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_46","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si30289_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"26","roles":{"answer":{"title":"type the answer here","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si30300","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_47","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si30304","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_48","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si30300_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"28","roles":{"answer":{"title":"type the answer here","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si30311","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_49","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si30315","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_50","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si30311_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"30","roles":{"answer":{"title":"type the answer here","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si30446","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_12","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide30523q1","for":"Slide30523q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si30458","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide30523q1","for":"Slide30523q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si30470","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide30523q1","for":"Slide30523q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si30386","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_19","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide30523q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si30373","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_18","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide30523q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si30405","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_20","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide30523q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si30354","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_17","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide30523q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide30523","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si30229","si30254","si30282","si30293","si30304","si30315","si30446","si30458","si30470","si30386","si30373"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide30523"},"question":{"interactionId":"30216","quizId":379,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"Type the question here","ikc":true,"type":"knowledgeCheck","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":["A"]}}},{"id":"si31027","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si31633","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"__fbbgitem_h8v11_10","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide30997q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si31034","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si31041","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si31049","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si31053","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si31049_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Wahr\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si31060","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si31064","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si31060_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Falsch\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si31094","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide30997q2","for":"Slide30997q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si31111","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide30997q2","for":"Slide30997q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si31124","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide30997q2","for":"Slide30997q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si31950","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide30997q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si31068","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide30997q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si31963","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide30997q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide30997","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si31027","si31034","si31053","si31064","si31094","si31111","si31124","si31068"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide30997"},"question":{"interactionId":"31014","quizId":379,"title":"Wahr/Falsch\r","text":"Type the question here","ikc":true,"type":"knowledgeCheck","interactionType":"true-false","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["A"]}}},{"id":"si31158","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si31165","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si31172","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si31177","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si31177_q1_answer_0_mc","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si31207","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide31136q3","for":"Slide31136q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si31224","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide31136q3","for":"Slide31136q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si31237","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide31136q3","for":"Slide31136q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si31181","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide31136q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si31996","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide31136q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si31983","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide31136q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide31136","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si31158","si31165","si31207","si31224","si31237","si31181"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide31136"},"question":{"interactionId":"31152","quizId":379,"title":"Lücken füllen\r","text":"Complete the sentence below by filling in the blanks.","type":"knowledgeCheck","ikc":true,"interactionType":"fill-in","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":[]}}},{"id":"Pool423","class":"pool","roles":{"pool":{"id":423,"name":"Pool1","questions":[]}}},{"id":"Grunddesign-Uni-Elearning","class":"project","title":"Grunddesign-Uni-Elearning","children":["Slide5366","Slide32251","Slide27179","Slide30524","Slide27916","Slide30523","Slide30997","Slide31136"],"roles":{"quiz":{"id":379,"branched":false,"submitAll":false,"review":true,"questions":["Slide27916q0","Slide30523q1","Slide30997q2","Slide31136q3"],"minScore":0,"maxScore":0,"passScore":0}}}],"contentSettings":{"global":{"branchAware":false},"toc":{"enabled":false},"playbar":{"enabled":true,"cc":false,"playPause":true,"back":true,"forward":true,"rewind":true,"close":true,"mute":true,"progressBar":true}},"contentReporting":{"CCCriteria":"launch_content","SCCriteria":"launch_content","exitNormalIfCompleted":false},"toc":[{"id":"Slide5366","title":"Slide 1"},{"id":"Slide32251","title":"Slide 2"},{"id":"Slide27179","title":"Content3"},{"id":"Slide30524","title":"Slide 4"},{"id":"Slide27916","title":"Slide 5"},{"id":"Slide30523","title":"Slide 6"},{"id":"Slide30997","title":"Slide 7"},{"id":"Slide31136","title":"Slide 8"}]}